leo.net 2010-06-21

# Welcome to Leomobile - Ringtones, wallpapers, games, Real tones

LEO strives to make sure that your privacy is protected any time you're using our services. You do need to give us some personal information so we're able to process your orders and requests. However, we want you to know what information we need, why we need it, and how we make sure that your information is protected. We want you to be able to enjoy your LEO experience safely and privately. 

### Your LEO account 

When you sign up with LEO, you establish a password-protected personal account for ordering ringtones, graphics, games and other items and services. 

### Information we need from you 

In order to establish your private LEO account and/or place an order, we need some personal information from you. This information may include contact information (such as name, email, cell phone number and address) and certain billing information, like a new cell phone number or change of carrier.   
We may occasionally request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and mailing address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the LEO service. 

### Changing your information 

To update your personal information, simply sign in and go to My Leo from your personal home page. You may also contact our Support team by writing infous@leo.net. You can make changes to your account information at any time. 

### E-mail notification of new LEO features and special offers

We will notify you about new features and services on LEO. We will always provide instructions to opt out from this service. We may send you site and service announcement updates with important information about the service. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements. 

### Sharing your information with third parties 

The personal information that you provide is an important part of our business. We are not in the business of selling this information to others. This information will only be shared with our direct partners and agents as required. 

### Cookies 

Cookies are pieces of information that your browser receives from Web sites and stores on your computer's hard drive. Information in cookies includes preferences you select while visiting a particular Web site. For example, by storing cookies on your hard drive, you'll return to a specific Web site with the same settings you used on a previous visit.   
LEO never saves your personal information on cookies. We do require cookies in order to manage and protect your LEO session, and if you choose, to store your e-mail address (so you don't have to type it in every time you log in). If you have cookies turned off, you will not be able to access LEO services. 

### Log files 

Our servers store IP addresses for all connections to the service. This data is analyzed in the aggregate and is not linked to your personal account. 

### Third Party Advertising 

Ads that appear on this Site may be delivered to users by a number of advertising partners that may change from time to time. Information about users' visits to this Site, such as the number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personally identifiable information), may be used to serve ads to users on this Site. 

### Legal exceptions to the rules 

Only in the case of our good-faith belief that the law requires it or, to protect your or our rights or property, will we disclose customer information to proper law enforcement authorities even though you might have sent us an e-mail requesting that we don't share your information. This information may be necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone who may attempt to cause injury to another's rights or property. 

### Notification of changes 

If our privacy policy changes, those changes will be posted to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are aware of the policy and applicable changes. 

### Your Acceptance of this Policy 

By visiting our Site, you signify your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Minors can only use our Site with the consent and involvement of their parent or guardian. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check our Site for updates. Any dispute as to these terms shall be governed by Italian law and subject to the courts of Rome, Italy. 

### Ownership 

One North America Inc. (11 Broadway, 10004, New York, NY, ID. Number 26-2070201) owns and operates LEO US and is the sole owner of the information collected on our Site.

### Contact Information 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at infous@leo.net
